Guide to the Stanford University, Women's Physical Education Department, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Records, 1928-1975
  - Women's P.E. Department - general files, 1920-1968
    - Budget, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - C, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - China colleges, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - Committee on Entertainment Fund, School of Education, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - Comptroller, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - Conferences, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - Conference -- School of Education, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - D, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - Dean of Women, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - E, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - Education, School of, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - Equipment, 1939-1940 (Box 8)
    - Examinations, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - F, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Forms and form letters, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - G, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - H, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Health reports, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Hospital Fund Committee -- Minutes, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - I, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - J, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - K, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - L, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Library, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Mc, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - M, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Medical Advisor of Men, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Minutes of staff meetings, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - N, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - O, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - P, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Personal, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
      Dr. Pryor's papers.
    - Physical examinations -- women, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Physical Therapy, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - President, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Publications (departmental), 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Public Health Committee, 1938-1940 (Box 9)
    - R, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Registrar, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Rental of Women's Gymnasium, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - S, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Statistics, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Statistics -- Health Service, 1933-1940 (Box 9)
    - Statistics -- Dr. Boynton, 1937-1940 (Box 9)
    - Sororities, 1938-1940 (Box 9)
    - T, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - U, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - University Health Service, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - W, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - Width-weight tables, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - X, Y, Z, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - YWCA, 1939-1940 (Box 9)
    - American Assoc. of Collegiate Registrars, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - American Student Health Association, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Applications and recommendations, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Appointments, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Budget, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Budget - Medical Dept., 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Budget - Physical Education Dept., 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Children's summer classes, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Comptroller, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Conferences, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Dean of Women, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Education, School of, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Equipment, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Forms and form letters, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Friends of China, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Fungus Study, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Insurance Assoc. of Approved Hospitals, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - K, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Knox Gelatine, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Library, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Men's Student Health Service, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Minutes of staff meetings, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
    - Personal, 1940-1941 (Box 9)
      Dr. Helen Pryor, Medical Director.
    - Physical Therapy, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - President, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - Public Health Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - Registrar, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - Rental of Women' s Gymnasium, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - School of Health Reorganization, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - Silver Burdett Company, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
      Correspondence re. health texts which Dr. Pryor co-authored.
    - Statistics, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - Student Hospital Fund Committee, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - Width-weight tables, 1940-1941 (Box 10)
    - A, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Accounting Department, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - American Student Health Association, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Applications and recommendations, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Appointments, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - B, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Budget, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
      Two folders.
    - Children's Summer Classes, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Committee to Study Housing, 1940-1942 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Dean of Women, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Education, School of, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Equipment, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Financial Vice-President, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Forms and form letters, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Health reports, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Home Nursing, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Hospital Service of California, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - League of Nations, 1940-1942 (Box 10)
    - Library, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Minutes of staff meetings, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Physical Education, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Physical Therapy, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Pink sheet, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - President, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Public Health Committee, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Registrar, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Rental of Women's Gymnasium, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Reprints, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - School of Health (Men), 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Sororities, 1940-1942 (Box 10)
    - Stanford Civilian Defense Council, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Statistics, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Student Health Fund Committee, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Swimming Pool, 1941-1942 (Box 10)
    - Accounting Department, 1942-1943 (Box 10)
    - American Student Health Asscciation, 1942-1943 (Box 10)
    - Appointments, 1942-1943 (Box 10)
    - Budget, 1942-1943 (Box 10)
    - California State Department of Education -- Conmission of Credentials, 1939-1943 (Box 10)
    - Curriculum Study, Society for, 1941-1944 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 10)
    - Dean of Women, 1942-1943 (Box 10)
    - Defence Council First Aid Exam, 1942-1943 (Box 10)
    - Education, School of, 1942-1944 (Box 10)
    - Education 177, 1941-1944 (Box 10)
    - Equipment, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Examinations, class, 1939-1943 (Box 11)
    - Faculty physical examinations, 1941-1944 (Box 11)
    - Financial Vice-President, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Guidance, 1939-1944 (Box 11)
    - Hospital Service of California, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Library, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Minutes of staff meetings, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Nursery School, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Nutrition and Dietetics, 1941-1943 (Box 11)
    - Nutrition and Dietetics requisitions, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Planning Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Physical Education, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Physical Therapy, 1942-1944 (Box 11)
    - President, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Public Health Committee, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Registrar, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Rental of Women's Gymnasium, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - S, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Scholarship, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - School of Health (Men), 1942-1943 (Box 10)
    - School of Health Education, 1939-1944 (Box 11)
    - Stanford Civilian Defense Council, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Statistics, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - Swimming Pool, 1942-1943 (Box 11)
    - A, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Accounting Department, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Alumni Review, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Appointments, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Budget, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Curriculum, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Dean of Women, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Equipment, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Financial Vice-President (Box 11)
    - Health reports, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Library, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Minutes of staff meetings, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Nutrition and Dietetics, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Physical Education, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Public Health Committee, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Registrar, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Rental of Women's Gymnasium, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - S, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - School of Health (Men), 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - State medicine, 1939-1945 (Box 11)
    - Statistics, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Swimming Pool, 1943-1944 (Box 11)
    - Tuberculosis Committee A.S.H.A., 1940-1944 (Box 11)
    - War Council, 1941-1944 (Box 11)
    - Yang, Ling Fu, 1942-1944 (Box 11)
    - Appointments, 1944-1945 (Box 11)
    - A.S.S.U., 1944-1945 (Box 11)
    - Budget, 1944-1945 (Box 11)
    - Correspondence, 1944-1945 (Box 11)
    - First Aid, 1941-1945 (Box 11)
    - Leave of Absence blanks, 1944-1945 (Box 11)
    - Library, 1944-1945 (Box 11)
    - Life Saving and Water Safety, 1941-1945 (Box 11)
    - Minutes of staff meeting, 1944-1945 (Box 11)
    - N.A.A.F., 1939-1945 (Box 11)
    - Rental of Women's Gymnasium, 1944-1945 (Box 11)
    - Rest Home, 1944-1945 (Box 11)
    - State Report, 1944-1945 (Box 11)
    - Statistics, 1944-1945 (Box 12)
    - Swimming Pool, 1944-1945 (Box 12)
    - Academic Council, Physical Education letter to, 1945-1946 (Box 12)
    - Budget, 1945-1946 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 12)
    - Equipment, 1945-1946 (Box 12)
    - Gymnasium, rental of, 1945-1946 (Box 12)
    - Library, 1945-1946 (Box 12)
    - Minutes of staff meetings, 1945-1946 (Box 12)
    - Orthopedic examinations, 1945-1946 (Box 12)
    - Physical Education, 1945-1946 (Box 12)
    - Swimming Pool, 1945-1946 (Box 12)
    - Budget, 1946-1947 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 12)
    - Library, 1946-1947 (Box 12)
    - Minutes of staff meetings, 1946-1947 (Box 12)
    - Physical Education, 1946-1947 (Box 12)
    - Publicity, 1946-1947 (Box 12)
    - Rental fees, 1946-1947 (Box 12)
    - School of Education, 1946-1947 (Box 12)
    - Swimming Pool, 1946-1947 (Box 12)
    - WAA, 1945-1947 (Box 12)
    - Appointments, 1945-1948 (Box 12)
    - Budget, 1947-1948 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, interdepartmental, 1946-1948 (Box 12)
    - Minutes, staff meetings, 1947-1948 (Box 12)
    - Physical Education, 1947-1948 (Box 12)
    - Pool, 1947-1948 (Box 12)
    - Shaw Dancers, 1947-1948 (Box 12)
    - Addresses for Summer Workshop, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Book lists for classes, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Budget, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, interdepartmental, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Library, 1947-1949 (Box 12)
    - Physical Education, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Pool statistics, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Rental of gym, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Riflery, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Staff budget, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Staff, Minutes of meeting, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Summer Workshop, evaluation, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Workshop reservations, 1948-1949 (Box 12)
    - Budget, 1949-1950 (Box 12)
    - Budget -- assistance, gifts, 1949-1950 (Box 12)
    - Clippings, 1949-1950 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, 1949-1950 (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, interdepartmental, 1949-1950 (Box 12)
    - Lifeguards, instructions, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Library, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Ojai tournament, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Physical Education, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Staff meetings, 1949-1950 (Box 13)
    - Budget, 1950-1951 (Box 13)
    - Budget -- assistance, gifts, 1950-1951 (Box 13)
    - Children's Class, summer, 1950-1951 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, interdepartmental, 1950-1951 (Box 13)
    - Examination questions, 1950-1951 (Box 13)
    - Ojai, 1951 Apr 26 (Box 13)
    - Physical Education, 1950-1951 (Box 13)
    - Rental of gym, 1949-1951 (Box 13)
    - Staff meeting Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 13)
    - Assistance Budget, 1951-1952 (Box 13)
    - Budget, 1951-1952 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1951-1952 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence -- interdepartmental, 1951-1952 (Box 13)
    - Ojai, 1951-1952 (Box 13)
    - Orthopedics, 1951-1952 (Box 13)
    - Physical Education, 1951-1952 (Box 13)
    - Staff meetings, 1951-1952 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 13)
    - Golf box and cart, 1952-1953 (Box 13)
    - Library, 1952-1953 (Box 13)
    - Majors, 1952-1953 (Box 13)
    - Physical Education, 1952-1953 (Box 13)
    - Staff meeting Minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 13)
    - Summer Workshop, inquiries re., 1952-1953 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 13)
    - Physical Education, 1953-1954 (Box 13)
    - Staff, 1953-1954 (Box 13)
    - Children's swim, 1953-1955 (Box 13)
    - Library, 1954-1955 (Box 13)
    - Life Saving and Water Safety certificates, 1954-1955 (Box 13)
    - Ojai, 1954-1955 (Box 13)
    - Physical Educatinn, 1954-1955 (Box 13)
    - Rest assignment reports, 1954-1955 (Box 13)
    - Staff Budget, 1954-1955 (Box 13)
    - Staff Minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 13)
    - Statistics on theory, 1948-1954 (Box 13)
    - Minutes of staff meeting, 1955-1956 (Box 13)
    - Modesto (Tennis), 1955-1956 (Box 13)
    - Physical Education, 1955-1956 (Box 13)
    - Registration, Mrs. Barr, 1950-1956 (Box 13)
    - Folk dancers -- Yosemite Park exhibition, 1956-1957 (Box 13)
    - Library, 1956-1957 (Box 13)
    - Medical notes, 1956-1957 (Box 13)
    - Parking, 1956-1957 (Box 13)
    - Physical Education, 1956-1957 (Box 13)
    - Sophomores, 1956-1957 (Box 13)
    - Swimming policies, 1956-1957 (Box 13)
    - Women on Faculty, 1956-1957 (Box 13)
    - Brochures & catalogues, 1957-1958 (Box 13)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 13)
    - Freshmen, incoming, 1957-1958 (Box 13)
    - Interim swim, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - Library, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - Noon swimming -- summer, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - Prerequisites, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - Rating sheets P.E. Majors, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - Staff Minutes, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - Summer Faculty, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - Summer Workshop, 1957-1958 (Box 14)
    - Correspondence -- interdepartmental, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
    - Dance concentration, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
    - Ice skating, skiing, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
    - Library, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
    - Physical Education for Women, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
    - Sports Workshop, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
    - Watson, Bobby, 1958-1959 (Box 14)
    - Accidents, 1949-1960 (Box 14)
    - Bulletin material -- P.E. Majors, 1959-1960 (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, interdepartmental, 1959-1960 (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, off-campus, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
    - Interim Swim, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
    - National Golf Tournament, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
    - Noon swim, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
    - Staff Budget, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
    - Staff Minutes, 1958-1960 (Box 15)
    - Use of building requests, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
    - Women's Clubhouse -- social dance, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
    - Workshop evaluations, 1959-1960 (Box 15)
    - Pool statistics, 1957-1962 (Box 15)
    - Blanks for car mileage, 1961-1962, undated (Box 15)
    - Curriculum and instruction courses, 1961-1962, undated (Box 15)
    - Departmental regulations (added 1979 May 22), 1946-1968 (Box 15)
  - Course materials, 1937-1970
    - Badminton, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Basketball, Undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Camping, 1938-1942 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Canoeing, 1937-1947 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Skiing - American Association For Health Physical Education and Recreation, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Skiing - California Skiing Association, Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Skiing - clubs, 1938-1947 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Skiing - competition, 1947-1948 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Skiing - exercises general, 1940-1946 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Skiing - exercises dry skiing, 1939-1948 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Skiing - Far West Ski Association, 1949-1950 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Skiing - films, 1937-1939 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Skiing - Fraser, Gretchen, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Skiing - Ski Illustrated, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Skiing - Stanford Ski Club, 1947-1949 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Skiing - Sun Valley, 1939-1942 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Skiing - miscellaneous correspondence, 1938-? (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Skiing - Gutherie, Luell W. "Snow or Straw - We Ski!", Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Soccer, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Softball - methods, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Softball - methods, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Speedball, 1950 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Swimming, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Tennis - class examinations, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Tennis - Tennis Committee, 1942 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Tennis - Tennis Guide, 1941-1942 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Tennis - Hazel Hotchkiss Whitman Cup, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Tennis - methods, 1938-1942 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Tennis - methods, 1948-1955, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Tennis - officiating, 1937-1965 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Tennis - ratings, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Tennis - spectatoring, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Tennis - terminology, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Tennis - Tri-Partite, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Tennis - MS. "Tennis Court Lay-out and Construction" and related correspondence, Undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Tennis - Guthrie, Luell W. and Georgia William "Tennis Court Lay- out and Construction", 1959 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Tennis - scorecards, Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Tennis - USLTA Women's National Collegiate Tennis Championship, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Tennis - miscellaneous papers, Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Tennis - dittos, Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Tennis - hand-outs, Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Track and Field, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Volleyball, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Education Courses 155-256, Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Education Courses 258, 1960-1961 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Leisure - Senior Colloquium, 1957-1961 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Leisure - Senior Colloquium, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Leisure - Senior Colloquium, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Leisure - Senior Colloquium, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Leisure - Senior Colloquium, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Leisure - Senior Colloquium, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Leisure - Senior Colloquium, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Leisure - Senior Colloquium, 1966 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Leisure - Senior Colloquium, 1968 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Leisure - Senior Colloquium, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Spectator course, 1938-1939 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda, reports, 1919-1975
    - American Student Health Association - Pacific Coast Section, 1934, 1936 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Calendars and schedules, Summer Quarter, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Calendars and schedules, Summer Quarter, 1954-1961 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - California Recreation Commission, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - National Section on Women's Athletics, 1939-1948 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Panama Street extension, 1962 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Memoranda, faculty-staff, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Memoranda, faculty-staff, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Memoranda, faculty-staff, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda, faculty-staff, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Departmental newsletter, 1968-1975 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Report to the President, 1919-1952 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Report to the President, 1952-1959 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Report to the President, 1959-1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Report to the President, 1966-1971 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous - extramural sports, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous - gymnastics, Danish, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous - gymnastics, Norwegian, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous - recreation reports, Undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous - Tri-Sports Day, 1938 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous - general publications and hand-outs, circa1938-1968 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous - general publications and hand-outs, Undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Undated
    All files are undated.
    - Badminton (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Basketball (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Dance - folk (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Dance - modern (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Golf (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Gymnastics (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Hockey (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Swimming (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Tennis (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Track and Field (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1982-027
  - Photographs - archery (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - archery (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Photographs - archery (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - badminton (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Photographs - basketball (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Photographs - bowling (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - conditioning (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Photographs - conditioning (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Photographs - conferences, 1939, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photographs - faculty (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Photographs - folk dancing (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Photographs - folk dancing [Spanish dancers, not from Stanford] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Photographs - folk dancing [negatives] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photographs - golf (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Photographs - golf (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Photographs - gymnastics, 1964, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - gymnastics (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Photographs - Mexican dance, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - miscellaneous (hockey, ice skating, canoeing) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Photographs - modern dance, 1972, undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Photographs - modern dance, 1957, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - modern dance, 1958, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Photographs - modern dance (older photos) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Photographs - modern dance, Charles Weidman, 1963 summer workshop faculty (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photographs - Polynesian workshop (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Photographs - recreation for the retarded (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Photographs - riding (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Photographs - riflery [negatives] (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Photographs - Roble Gym, 1938-1966, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Photographs - ski conditioning, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Photographs - softball, 1955, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Photographs - swimming (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Photographs - swimming, 1955-1973, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Photographs - swimming [color transparencies], 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Photographs - tennis, 1963-1972, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Photographs - tennis, 1969-1974, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Photographs - tennis, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - track and field (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Photographs - volleyball, 1950, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - WRA board, 1967, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Archery techniques chart, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous clippings (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous newsletter, programs, etc., 1933-1982 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Film - swimming; color; [8mm ?] (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Bay Area Sports Day, first place ribbon, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - WRA Handbook (bound), 1940-1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Records, Accession ARCH-1984-132
  - Class: Community Recreation: correspondence and teaching notes, 1956 Fall (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Class: Community Recreation: course materials, 1956 Fall (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class: Community Recreation: course materials, 1956 Fall (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Class: Dance: course materials, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Class: Dance Research: student work, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Class: Dance Research: student work, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Class: Dance Research: student work, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Class: Dance Research: student work, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Class: Dance Research: student work, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Class: Dance Research: student work, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Class: Dance Research: student work, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Class: Leisure in the Modern World (Senior Colloquium): course materials, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Class: Leisure in the Modern World (Senior Colloquium): course materials, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Class: Leisure in the Modern World, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Class: Tennis, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Class: Tennis, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)